Finding Aid to the Save the Redwoods League photograph collection. 1885-2014
The Bancroft Library
- Series 1: Vertical Files., 1897-2014; cartons 1-8; A box 1; AX box 1, folders 1-20; B box 1, folders 1-15, 17-18; C box 1; D folder 1; F folder 1; H folder 1; NEG boxes 1-5; NEG(gl) boxes 1, 3, 8, 9; NNEG boxes 1-6
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 71-500., 1971 (Carton 6)
    Jessamine Rugg and Morrill Goddard Memorial Redwood Grove, Robert and Leona Train Rienow Redwood Grove, James W. Buel Memorial Grove, Rexford W. Barton Grove, Christopher Mabley Granger Grove, Lucy H. Hume Memorial Grove, Ella Goad Hooker and Charles Osgood Hooker Memorial Grove, Mary Kellogg Jensen Grove (seashore), Alfred and Elizabeth Kay Grove and Grove Addition, Pleasant Memories Grove, Chauncey P. Pond, Jr. Memorial Grove, Elizabeth E.B. Roberts Memorial Grove, Karl and Sophie Rothschild Memorial Grove and Grove X 156.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 71-501., 1971 (Carton 6)
    Groves X 53A, X 146A, X 148A, X 148B, X 150A, X 151, X 152, X 153, X 154, X 154A, X 156, X 174, and X 175.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 71-502., 1971 (Carton 6)
    Grove X 178, Grove X 181, Grove X 183, Grove X 190A, Grove X 190D, Section 4, Section 9, and Alexander Lincoln Prairie.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 72-500., 1972 (Carton 6)
    Elaine Berke Grove, Edward D. and Nella K. Armstrong Memorial Grove, Grove X 163, William W. Eastman Grove, Alan and Margaret Kempner Grove, Valentin and Dorothy Korbus Grove, and Arjay and Frances Miler Grove.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 73-500., 1973 (Carton 6)
    Aaron Davis Memorial Grove, Pinkston Wade Laird Memorial Grove, and Leonard and Marguerite Liermann Grove.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 74-500., 1974 (Carton 6)
    Alan and Margaret Kempner Grove, Grove X 129C and Grove X 163C.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 75-500., 1975 (Carton 6)
    Ethel Hulbert Bloodgood Grove and Mary Wheeler Memorial Grove.
    Photographs by John Gutteridge and Howard King.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 76-500., 1976 (Carton 6)
    Frank P. Belotti Grove, Elaine Berke Grove, Paul Strong Achilles Memorial Grove, Forever Grove, George M. and Mary Hansen McDaniel Grove and Alice McCutchen Schmiedell Grove.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 77-500., 1977 (Carton 7)
    Harold C. Bradley Memorial Grove, Henry Paul Busch and Lydia Leaming Busch Memorial Grove, William W. Eastman Grove, Grove X 149B, Grove X 157, Grove X 155, Joy-Laton Grove, Emmett and Edna Koster and Doane and Deborah Merrill Grove, Gertrude and Philip Leslie Grove, William Bradford Meisner and John Milton Meisner Memorial Grove, and Mr. and Mrs. Eugen Neuhaus Redwood Grove.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 77-501., 1977 (Carton 7)
    Margaret and Nathaniel Owings Redwood Grove, Pleasant Memories Grove Addition, Grove X 157, Grove X 158, Grove X 162 A1, Grove X 162B, Grove X 162 D, Grove X 164 and, Groves X 166 through X 170.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 77-502., 1977 (Carton 7)
    Groves X 171, X 172, X 173, X 174, X 175, X 176, X 178, X 179, X 180, X 182, and X 184.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 78-500., 1978 (Carton 7)
    Harold C. Bradley Grove, Frank J. and Isabelle V. Dore Grove, Grove X 187B, Grove X 187D, Grove X 188A, Grove X 188 B, and Grove X 188D.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 97-500., 1997 (Carton 7)
    Groves X 167, X 168C through X 168F, X 169 B, X 169 C, X 180D, X 181A, and X 202.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 97-501., 1997 (Carton 7)
    Groves X 169 A, X 170A, 172A-H, X 173G, 175B, X 178B - X 178E, X 179B1, X 179B2, X 180A, X 180C, X 180D, X 181A, and X 181B.
  - Pronsolino Property., circa 2005? (Carton 7)
    Includes color snapshots, a letter soliciting funds to purchase the property and a map.
    25 matching 35mm negatives removed to NEG box 2.
  - Purisima Creek Redwoods Open Space Preserve, Midpeninsula Regional Open Space District (San Mateo County). (Carton 7)
  - Reagan, Ronald, at presentation of funds for Pepperwood., March 13, 1968 (Carton 7)
    Presentation to Governor of California of $7,000,000 for Pepperwood Grove addition to Humboldt Redwoods State Park. Includes Governor Ronald Reagan, Frank Belotti, Norman B. Livermore, Newton B. Drury, Randolph Collier, Ralph Chaney and John B. Dewitt.
    1 matching copy negative removed to NEG box 5.
  - Redwood Creek and Emerald Creek Watershed., circa 1925-1972 (Carton 7)
    Includes aerial views, Skunk Cabbage Creek area and Lost Man Creek area.
    Includes photographs by Drury, Howard King, Martin Litton and Lawrence C. Merriam.
    3 matching copy negatives removed to NEG box 3. 1 matching negative removed to NNEG box 6.
  - Redwood Highway., circa 1920-circa 1950 (Carton 7)
    General images of the Redwood Highway and attractions along the road. Bulk are of Humboldt County. Includes the Benbow Hotel and exterior of C. Warren Howe camera pictorialist studio.
    Includes photographs by Tibbitts, Martin, Freeman and Moulin.
    See also Del Norte Coast Redwood State Park and Humboldt Redwoods State Park for images identified as being in the parks.
    3 negatives (2 matching and 1 related) removed to NNEG box 6.
    - Redwood Highway in North Dyerville Flat., [circa 1920s?]; BANC PIC 2006.030--PIC; 1 photograph (Carton 7)
      Dirt road through the redwood forest in Humboldt County.
      Numbered 2031.
      This material was selectively digitized from a larger resource or collection. From folder: Redwood Highway.
      Coast redwood -- California -- Pictorial works; Landscape photographs; Humboldt County (Calif.)
  - Redwood National Park (Humboldt County and Del Norte County)., circa 1930-1992 (Carton 7)
    Includes Lady Bird Johnson at Redwood National Park dedication, Emerald Creek, Howland Hill Road, Tall Trees area and map of Redwood Park.
    Includes photographs by Moulin Studios, David Swanlund, Howard King and Mary Angle-Franzini.
    2 matching and 3 related copy negatives (copies of same image) removed to NEG box 5.
  - Redwood National Park, oversize., Before November 29, 1965 (C box 1, Folder 11)
    2 maps Topographical map of proposed Redwoods National Park (2 copies).
    Received November 29, 1965 from National Park service.
  - Redwood National Park -- Dedication of Lady Bird Johnson Grove., August 27, 1969 (Carton 7)
    2 matching negatives removed to NEG box 5.
  - Redwood National Park -- Dedication of Lady Bird Johnson Grove, oversize., August 27, 1969; 1 photograph (Ax box 1)
    Color photograph by David Swanlund.
  - Redwood National Park -- Dedication of Lady Bird Johnson Grove, oversize., August 27, 1969; 1 photograph (C box 1, Folder 11)
    Color photograph by David Swanlund. Mounted on board.
  - Redwood National Park -- Dedication of Lady Bird Johnson Grove, oversize., August 27, 1969; 1 photograph (F folder 1)
  - Redwood National Park -- Dedication of Lady Bird Johnson Grove -- Wainwright photographs., August 27, 1969 (Carton 7)
    Photographs by Bob Wainwright.
  - Redwood National Park -- Dedication of Newton B. Drury Visitor Center., October 1973 (Carton 7)
  - Redwood National Park -- Dedication as World Heritage Site., May 22, 1982 (Carton 7)
    - "Redwood National Park World Heritage dedication, Lost Man Creek Picnic Area.", May 22 1982; Swanlund, David; BANC PIC 2006.030--PIC; 1 photograph (Carton 7)
      Congressman Don Clausen; Russell Dickerson, Director of National Park Service; Bob Barbee, Superintendent of Redwood National Park.
      Photograph 5106.
      This material was selectively digitized from a larger resource or collection. From folder: Redwood National Park -- Dedication as World Heritage Site.
      National parks & reserves -- California
  - Redwood National Park -- Little Lost Man Creek., 1964-1965 (Carton 7)
    Photographs by Martin Litton.
  - Redwood National Park -- Logging., 1968-1977 (Carton 7)
    Includes hand drawn map of logging plans.
    Includes photographs by Dennis Brokaw.
  - Redwood National Park -- Logging -- Arcata Redwood property., 1964-1966 (Carton 7)
    Land owned by, or formerly owned by, Arcata Redwood Company, which is adjacent to Redwoods National Park, or became part of the Park.
  - Redwood National Park -- Logging -- King photographs., 1969-1971 (Carton 7)
  - Redwood National Park -- Logging -- Swanlund aerial views., 1975-1977; 2 folders (Carton 7)
    Photographs by David Swanlund. Includes Arcata Redwood Company property.
    12 negatives (9 matching and 3 related) removed to NEG box 5.
  - Redwood National Park -- Logging -- Van de Mark photographs., 1969-1974 (Carton 7)
    Photographs by David Van de Mark.
  - Redwood National Park -- Logging -- Van de Mark photographs -- Aerial views., 1973-1978 (Carton 7)
  - Redwood National Park -- Skunk Cabbage Creek., 2003 (Carton 7)
    29 negatives (26 matching and 3 related) removed to NEG box 2.
  - Redwood National Park -- Skunk Cabbage Creek -- Aerial views., 1970-1976 (Carton 7)
    Includes photographs by David Swanlund and Martin Litton.
  - Redwood National Park -- Skunk Cabbage Creek -- Swanlund photographs., 1974 (Carton 7)
  - Redwood National Park -- Split Rock., 1969 (Carton 7)
    Includes John B. Dewitt. Photographs by Howard King.
  - Redwood National Park -- Tall Trees Grove., 1964-1967 (Carton 7)
    Includes area around Tall Trees Grove, aerial views, the Tall Tree Committee, and the Tall Tree, or Libby Tree, formerly the tallest tree.
    Includes photographs by Howard King, Martin Litton and Lawrence C. Merriam
    2 matching copy negative (2 copies of same image) removed to NEG box 3.
  - Redwood National Park -- Tall Trees Grove area -- Shrawder photograph., circa 1968 (Carton 7)
    Photograph by John F. Shrawder.
  - Redwood National Park -- Tall Trees Grove area-- Swanlund photographs., 1964-1980 (Carton 7)
    Photographs by David Swanlund. Includes Lawrence C. Merriam, Newton B. Drury T.A. Greig, Alfred H. Merrill and Ralph W. Chaney together with the Tallest Tree in the background; Tall Trees Grove; Redwood Creek; aerial views.
    2 matching copy negatives and 1 color slide (not numbered) removed to NEG box 5.
  - Redwood National Park -- Tall Trees Grove area-- Swanlund photographs, album., April 1964 (Carton 7)
    Notebook type album of photographs by David Swanlund titled, "Tallest tree and second tallest tree, Redwood Creek, Humboldt County, Calif." 2 copies.
  - Redwood National Park -- Tall Trees Grove area -- Swanlund photographs, oversize., May 29, 1964; 2 photographs (Ax box 1, Folder 18)
    Includes Lawrence C. Merriam, Newton B. Drury T.A. Greig, Alfred H. Merrill and Ralph W. Chaney together with the Tallest Tree in the background.
  - Redwood National Park -- Ulrich photographs., 1976-1980 (Carton 7)
    Photographs by Larry Ulrich. Includes Lost Man Creek, Bald Hills Road and Lady Bird Johnson Grove.
  - Redwood National Park -- White House meeting with President Johnson., June 25, 1964 (Carton 7)
    Meeting about proposed Redwoods National Park. Includes David Brower, Senator Thomas Kuchel, Undersecretary Carr, Congressman Aspinall, Tony Smith, Melvil1e B. Grosvenor, Conrad L. Wirth, Oscar L. Chapman, George Hertzog, Chester Brown, William Siri, Stewart Udall, President Lyndon B. Johnson, Earl Warren and Senator Clinton Anderson.
  - Redwood National Park -- White House signature ceremony., October 2, 1968 (A box 1, Folder 10)
    President Johnson, Lady Bird Johnson and John B. Dewitt at the White House signing of act establishing Redwood National Park.
  - Redwood National Park -- 97-500., 1997 (Carton 7)
    Skunk Cabbage area. Photographs by Evan Johnson.
  - Redwood trees., circa 1920s- circa 2000; 2 folders (Carton 7)
    Miscellaneous images of redwood trees and burls.
    Includes photographs by Freeman Art Co. and Gabriel Moulin.
    1 matching negative removed to NEG box 3. 1 matching negative removed to NNEG box 4.
  - Redwood trees, oversize., 2 photographs and 2 drawings (A box 1, Folder 11)
    Photographs are of a horse and buggy in the forest, and of a cabin in the forest. Drawings are of a man standing next to a redwood tree.
  - Redwood trees, oversize., 3 photographs (Ax box 1, Folder 19)
    All are color. 2 photographs are copies of same image.
  - Redwood trees, oversize., 1 painting (B box 1, Folder 12)
    Painting by Manuel.
  - Redwood trees, oversize., 4 photographs (B box 1, Folder 18)
    "Sugar Pine and Big Bear," San Bernardino Co., by Albert E. Thompson. "The Firs by the Trail," by C.D. Pettit. Redwood tree, by E.F. Martin Studio, Eureka (signed on back). Forest with light coming through trees, by C.K. Herr.
    All photographs are mounted on paper.
  - Redwood trees, oversize., 3 photographs (C box 1, Folder 12)
    Color photographs of unidentified locations.
  - Redwood trees, oversize., circa 1920?; 1 photograph (H folder 1)
    Panoramic landscape of redwood forest with dirt road and man. Photograph by E.R. Freeman.
  - Redwood trees -- Automobiles with. (Carton 7)
    Bulk are of unknown locations. Includes an automobile in a drive-thru tree.
  - Redwood trees -- Automobiles with, oversize., circa 1920s?; 1 photograph (B box 1, Folder 18)
    Mounted photograph by David P. Eastman.
  - Redwood trees -- Events or history in the life of., circa 1920, 1945 (Carton 7)
    Includes child next to labeled rings of tree cross section; "History in the Life of a Redwood Tree," flier with illustration of historical events alongside a redwood tree.
  - Redwood trees -- Events or history in the life of, oversize., 1930s?; 3 items (C box 1, Folder 2)
    "Events in the Life of a Big Tree," poster (3 copies).
  - Redwood trees -- Events or history in the life of, oversize., 1960; 1 print (D folder 1)
    "Redwoods Endures the Ages," color poster.
    Copyright: The Pacific Lumber Company.
  - Redwood trees -- People with., 1928-1951, undated; 3 folders (Carton 7)
    People posing next to, on or in redwood trees. Bulk are unknown locations. Includes Sherman Hendee and his horse.
    Includes photographs by Hickey, P.M. Schmook and Moulin Studios.
  - Redwoods of the Past (booklet)., 1965? (Carton 7)
    Photographs used in publication. Many are duplicates of Dawn Redwood (Metasequoia) photographs.
    6 copy negatives (4 matching and 3 related) removed to NEG box 5.
  - Redwoods of the Past (booklet), oversize., 1965? (C box 1, Folder 13)
    1 map of world distribution of redwood trees. Used in publication.
  - Reynolds Redwoods., received February 1963 (Carton 7)
    4 matching copy negatives removed to NEG box 5.
  - Richardson Grove State Park (Humboldt County)., 1928-1978 (Carton 7)
    Includes people swimming in river and camping and campground marker, Richardson Grove, James W. Toumey Grove, and slide on McMeekan Tract.
    Includes photographs by E.N. Fairchild, Freeman Art Co., Drury, H.W. Shepherd, E. French, Gordon H. Lord and David Van de Mark.
    1 CD with 1 image removed to NEG box 3.
  - Richardson Grove State Park, oversize., circa 1940?; 1 photograph (Ax box 1, Folder 20)
    Man standing next to cross section of a redwood tree (oversize duplicate copy print).
  - Richardson Grove State Park, oversize., circa 1925?; 1 photograph (G folder 1)
    Panorama of people standing in front of redwood trees and cabins
    Title from back of photo. Memorial grove established in 1922.
  - Russian Gulch State Park (Mendocino County)., 1930, undated (Carton 7)
    Includes photograph by Moulin and Wonacott's Studio.
  - Samuel P. Taylor State Park (Marin County)., 1939-1954 (Carton 7)
    Includes KCBS (radio station) document
  - San Francisco., circa 1925-1930; 2 photographs and 1 drawing (B box 1, Folder 13)
    Native Sons of the Golden West monument and fountain. Pioneer Monument at Civic Center, by Gabriel Moulin. Drawing of San Francisco skyline.
  - San Mateo County., November 1981 (Carton 7)
    Heritage Grove. Photographs by Phil McFaul.
  - Santa Cruz County. (Carton 7)
    Includes coast and redwoods.
  - Save the Redwoods League., 1900-1987 (Carton 7)
    Various people involved, with and events related to the history of Save-the-Redwoods League. Includes copy photograph of the first Save the Redwoods gathering (original removed to oversize B); Mrs. A.J. Monroe, Mrs. Kate Harpst, Frank Silence (driver), Mrs. T. Atkinson and Mrs. Fred Georgeson in front of an automobile with a Save the Redwoods sign in Sequoia Park, Eureka; William E. Colby, Duncan McDuffie and John P. Buwalda at Yosemite National Park; group portrait of Annual Meeting of the Council; various award presentations.
  - Save the Redwoods League, oversize., 1900; 1 photograph (B box 1)
    Group portrait of the first "Save the Redwoods" gathering.
    - First "Save the Redwoods" gathering., May 1900; BANC PIC 2006.030--B; 1 photograph (B box 1, Folder 1)
      Group portrait, left to right: ?; Dr. Jordan; Prof. Dudley; ?; Prof Stillman; I.Q. Packard; Lt. Governor Jeter; Judge Richards; Mrs. Carrie Stevens Walters; ?; Col. Chas. B. Wing; Prof. Montgomery; ?; Prof. Green.
      Photograph by Andrew P. Hill.
  - Save the Redwoods League -- Member photographs for publication., 2002? (Carton 7)
    Dr. Jules Riskin standing in front of wall of Honor Cards, which commemorate trees planted in honor of his wife and him by friends and family members.
    3 matching and related 35mm negatives (1 strip) removed to NEG box 2.
  - Save the Redwoods League -- Office -- 003-001., June 12, 2003 (Carton 7)
    Hattie's party.
  - Save the Redwoods League -- Semi-centennial photographs., June 15-16, 1968 (Carton 7)
    Semi-centennial ceremony of Save the Redwoods League at Pepperwood in Humboldt Redwoods State Park, and dinner held at the Eureka Inn. Includes Newton B. Drury, Thomas A. Greig, David Canfield, Mrs. Harmon C. Bell, Frank E. Sylvester, Harthon L. Bill, William Penn Mott, Jr.
    Includes photographs by David Swanlund
    1 matching color slide and 1 duplicate copy negative removed to NEG box 5. 1 matching negative removed to NEG box 3.
  - Save the Redwoods League -- Seventy-fifth anniversary celebration., October 2, 1993 (Carton 7)
    Includes John B. Dewitt speaking in the Founders' Grove.
  - Save the Redwoods League -- Seventy-fifth anniversary celebration -- Johnson contact sheets., October 1993 (Carton 7)
    Event held in the Founders' Grove. Photographs by Evan Johnson.
    Matching negatives removed to NEG box 2.
    See also: album volumes 6-7.
  - Save the Redwoods League -- Staff lunch honoring Sherry Busalacchi for 20 year service., April 3, 1987 (Carton 7)
  - Save the Redwoods League -- Staff trips -- Arcata redwood conference., June 1996 (Carton 7)
  - Save the Redwoods League -- Staff trips -- Big Basin., 2002 (Carton 7)
    27 matching negatives removed to NEG box 2.
  - Save the Redwoods League -- Staff trips --Canoeing., October 2004 (Carton 7)
    23 matching and related negatives removed to NEG box 2. 1 photo CD removed to NEG box 3.
  - Scotia Inn., 1910, 1962 (Carton 8)
    Copy photographs.
  - Sequoia and Kings Canyon National Parks (Tulare and Fresno Counties)., 1920s, 1948, 1987-1989 (Carton 8)
    Bulk are color snapshots. Includes Garfield Grove and a graph comparison of Hart and Sherman Trees.
    1 matching negative removed to NEG box 5.
  - Sequoia and Kings Canyon National Parks, oversize., circa 1920?; 1 photograph (B box 1, Folder 14)
    General Grant Tree. Photograph by B. Janeith Knight.
  - Sequoia and Kings Canyon National Parks, oversize., June 1986; 1 photograph (D folder 5)
    Giant Forest, Broken Arrow prescribed burn ignited by the National Park Service.
  - Sequoia and Kings Canyon National Parks -- Fire., 1991 (Carton 8)
    Color snapshots of a fire. Includes Pearson Henderson Memorial Grove, Margaret Sweasey Memorial Grove and Kaweah Han.
  - Sequoia and Kings Canyon National Parks -- Garfield Grove., June 1987; 1 photograph (B box 1, Folder 15)
    Color, matted photograph by Don Briggs.
  - Sequoia and Kings Canyon National Parks -- President Bill Clinton's visit., 2000? (Carton 8)
  - Sequoia City Park, Eureka., circa 1920?, 1969 (Carton 8)
    Includes forested areas nearby.
    Photographs by Freeman Foto, Patterson and Bob Wainwright.
  - Sequoia National Forest (Fresno, Kern and Tulare Counties) -- Bearskin Grove, Hume Lake District., April 27, 1986 (Carton 8)
    Area clear-cut of non-sequoias in 1982 and/or 1983, and burned in the fall of 1984.
    Photographs by Dwight Willard.
    Snapshots removed from an album.
  - Sequoia National Forest -- Black Mountain Grove, Tule Ranger District., June 8, 1986 (Carton 8)
    Area along Forest Service Road 21S12, north of Solo Peak, showing some logging of non-sequoias in progress. Labeled the Solo Peak sale by the Forest Service.
  - Sequoia National Forest -- Dillonwood Grove., 1991-2000 (Carton 8)
    Includes photographs and maps used in a report.
  - Sequoia National Forest -- Dillonwood Grove -- 01-004., 2001 (Carton 8)
    25 matching and related negatives (35mm negative strips) removed to NEG box 2.
  - Sequoia National Forest -- Dillonwood Grove -- 02-010., 2002 (Carton 8)
    26 matching and related negatives (35mm negative strips) removed to NEG box 2.
  - Sequoia National Forest -- Litton photographs., October 1988 (Carton 8)
    Four color 35mm slides by Martin Litton. Includes Black Mountain Grove.
  - Shriners Hospital fountain with redwood motif., 1941-1942 (Carton 8)
    Background screen with redwood motif for fountain in the physical therapy unit at Shriners' Hospital for Children in San Francisco. Designed by Olas C. Malmquist based on a Moulin photograph of Avenue of the Giants.
  - Shriners redwood tree planting ceremony., May 16, 1971 (Carton 8)
    At Shriners Hospital for Crippled Children in San Francisco.
  - Sinkyone Wilderness State Park (Mendocino County)., 1975-1986 (Carton 8)
    Includes former Frank Look Property on Mattole River and John B. Dewitt.
    Photographs by Dan Briggs, David Swanlund and Brad Welton.
    - Jackass Creek watershed owned by the Georgia-Pacific Corporation, Sinkyone Wilderness State Park., February 1986; BANC PIC 2006.030--PIC; 1 photograph (Carton 8)
      Bird's-eye view of coast from forested ridge.
      Photograph by Brad Welton.
      This material was selectively digitized from a larger resource or collection. From Folder: Sinkyone Wilderness State Park.
      Coast redwood -- California -- Pictorial works; Landscape photographs; Mendocino County (Calif.)
  - Sinkyone Wilderness State Park -- 86-500., 1986 (Carton 8)
    Barnum Property. Photograph by Dan Briggs. Folder only contains 1 item.
  - Smith River (Del Norte County)., circa 1920s-1986 (Carton 8)
    Photographs by McCurry, Bill Roman, Larry Ulrich and Van Pierce Miller.
  - Smith River, oversize., 1973; 1 photograph (C box 1, Folder 14)
    South Fork of the Smith River. Matted and signed photograph by Bill Roman.
  - Smith River -- Briggs photographs., January 1988 (Carton 8)
    Photographs by Dan Briggs.
    Matching negatives in NEG box 4.
  - Sonoma County., 1928-1938 (Carton 8)
    Includes Moses Hopkins timber near Healdsburg, Russian River, coast north of Fort Ross, Vallejo Home State Monument and church built from one redwood tree in Santa Rosa.
    Includes photographs by Moulin, Lawton and Newton B. Drury.
  - Standish Hickey State Park (Mendocino County)., 1974 (Carton 8)
    Bulk are of Ray Taber Property. Includes a hand drawn map of area.
    Photographs by David Swandlund.
  - Standish Hickey State Park -- 74-500., 1974 (Carton 8)
    Photographs by David Swandlund and Howard King.
  - Stout, Frank D. (Carton 8)
    Studio portrait by Eugene Hutchinson, Chicago.
  - Symmes, Day W., bequest property -- Coastal property., 1967-1971 (Carton 8)
    Snapshots of former Day Symmes property near Gualalla.